Contact

+61412126599 (Mobile) ivan.rahn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ivanran (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Financial Accounting
Accounting
Tax

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Russian (Native or Bilingual)
German (Elementary)

Honors-Awards
Scholarship

Ivan Ran

Accountant at a migration agency, undergoing the CPA qualification Sydney, Australia

Summary

My experience, both overseas and in Australia, as well as entrepreneurial spirit and understanding of accounting are some of the reasons why my interests at work are focused on solutions that optimise business processes.

The initiated projects I offered in my previous employment resulted in increased automation of business processes, improved cash flow and feedback to the management.

With a solid experience in all day-to-day and month-end accounting functions I am currently half way through my CPA study and looking forward to learning new skills.

Experience

Prudential Migration and Education Consultancy Pty Ltd Accountant and Office Manager May 2015 - Present

Sydney, Australia

Initiated projects include:

Implementing an Accounting Software Package (MYOB), Some notable results were:

- 30% decrease in bad debts
- 75% decrease in Accounts Receivable and payable processing time
- Increase of the Accounts Receivable turnover.

Optimising business processes, leading to a 2% decrease on business expenses.

Facilitating flow of accounting and managerial information, which helped the directors to identify areas with higher potential and shift more resources to those areas.

Co-developing new customer relationship management database, allowing better allocation of workload and increased customer retention.

Cooperating with the marketing director to increase the online presence of the company, resulting in 10% increase in new customers.

Australia Grace Home Education Bookkeeper April 2014 - May 2015 (1 year 2 months) Sydney, Australia

Developed and implemented Accounts Receivable system to issue and track the invoices resulting in recovery of over \$20,000 of unpaid debts and reducing receivables processing time by more than 50%.

i-Ran Light & Sound Rentals Manager 2010 - 2014 (5 years) Sydney, Australia

Co-founded and managed a sound and lighting equipment rental business. In charge of staff acquisition, daily operations and finance.

PKF MCD
Assistant Auditor
November 2007 - January 2009 (1 year 3 months)
Saint Petersburg, Russian Federation

Trained new team members, helped in developing Excel templates for audit processes.

Education

Coder Academy
Diploma of IT, Web Development · (2018 - 2019)

University of New South Wales Bachelor, Accounting (2009 - 2011)

Saint Petersburg State University Specialist, Accounting (2005 - 2009)